{
    "subject": "resource/Faiz_Ahmad_Faiz",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Communist_Party_of_Pakistan",
    "human_readable": "Faiz Ahmad Faiz was a part of the Communist Party of Pakistan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9328843355178833,
            "question": "With which Pakistani political party was Faiz Ahmad Faiz connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.908882200717926,
            "question": "What political party was Faiz Ahmad Faiz a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8905084133148193,
            "question": "Faiz Ahmad Faiz's affiliation was with which Pakistani political organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8206769824028015,
            "question": "To which political party did Faiz Ahmad Faiz belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8131980299949646,
            "question": "What was the name of the political party that Faiz Ahmad Faiz was associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.762758195400238,
            "question": "Was Faiz Ahmad Faiz a member of any political groups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6531769633293152,
            "question": "What is known about Faiz Ahmad Faiz's political involvement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6382439136505127,
            "question": "Was Faiz Ahmad Faiz involved in any political organizations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.536835253238678,
            "question": "Did Faiz Ahmad Faiz have any political affiliations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4939197301864624,
            "question": "What political ideology did Faiz Ahmad Faiz likely subscribe to based on his affiliations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Faiz Ahmad Faiz was a part of the Communist Party of Pakistan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8720_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Faiz Ahmad Faiz have any political affiliations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8720_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Faiz Ahmad Faiz involved in any political organizations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8720_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Faiz Ahmad Faiz's political involvement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8720_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8720_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Faiz being associated with the Communist Party of Pakistan. He founded it in 1947 along with Sajjad Zaheer and Jalaludin Abdur Rahim, and was a well-known communist in the country. Additionally, he remained a lifelong Marxist even after disagreeing with some aspects of the party."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Faiz was associated with the Communist Party of Pakistan, founding it in 1947 along with other individuals. Therefore, the statement that Faiz Ahmad Faiz was a part of the Communist Party of Pakistan is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}